You know, I'm thinking about letting Emma have her first cookie.
我琢磨着该给艾玛吃第一块饼干了
Her first cookie? She has cookies all the time.
第一块？她常吃饼干
I've never given her a cookie.
我没喂过她饼干
- Have you? - No.
-你给她了？ -没有！
No. And for the record, I've also never given her frosting from a can.
另外，我也没从罐子里拿糖给她。
Hey, Rach, the adoption agency needs letters of recommendation..
瑞秋，领养中心要我们交一份推荐信。
and we wondered if you would write one for us?
你愿意帮我们写一封吗？
- Of course. I would be honored. - Thank you.
-乐意效劳，我的荣幸 -谢谢
I think there's been an oversight.
怎么不找我？
We would have asked you. We thought you wouldn't be interested.
乔伊，我们本想找你，但又觉得你可能没兴趣
It's just that we don't think of you as really being so much with the words.
我们觉得你可能不擅长跟文字打交道
Clearly, we were wrong.
看样子我们错了
I got a lot of nice stuff to say about you guys, okay?
对于你们二位，我有很多好话可写
I know how much you want to have a baby..
而且我也非常清楚你们多想要个BB
and I would love to help you get one.
我很想帮你们
You know what? Then we want you to do it.
好吧，乔伊，你来写
Thank you. All right. Let me see how I'm gonna start.
谢谢，我想想怎么开头。
"Dear Baby Adoption Decider People.."
亲爱的婴孩领养权决定人：
So excited about your letter.
迫不及待想看你写的推荐信。
- Hey. - Hey, Phoebe.
-嘿！ -嘿！菲比！
- Wow, don't you look nice. - Yes, I do.
-你可真好看！ -没错，是很美
Today's Mike and my one-year anniversary.
今天麦克和我庆祝一周年。
What's it the anniversary of?
啥的周年？
Your first date, your first kiss, first time you had sex?
第一次亲吻？第一次上床？
Yeah.
对。
So you must be going somewhere fancy to celebrate.
你们会去好地方隆重庆祝？
A Knicks game.
看尼克斯队篮球比赛。
Aren't you a little overdressed?
你好象穿得过于隆重？
I've never had a one-year anniversary before..
我从未和哪个男人有过一周年。
so no matter where we go, I'm wearing something fancy..
所以不管去哪里庆祝，我一定要盛装打扮
I'm gonna put on my finest jewelry..
带最好的珠宝
and we're gonna have sex in a public restroom.
还要在公共洗手间嘿咻。
You guys do that?
是吗？
Chandler won't even have sex in our bathroom.
钱德连在我家洗手间嘿咻也不肯
That's where people make number two.
洗手间是尿尿的地方！
The One Where Rachel's Sister Babysits
rainystar压制iPod-MP4
So, you know, I have a little time if you want to..
我有点时间，你想不想
I'd love to, but I really have to grade these papers.
好想，但是要给卷子评分
Fine. It's fine.
好，那好吧
I'll just shower by myself.
那我就自己去洗澡
B. B. B. B. B.
“B”、"B"……
You gave a B to a Pottery Barn catalog.
你给陶器目录也打了个"B"
Well, it had some good ideas. Take off your shirt.
他们表现尚可。脱衣服吧
- Damn it. - Rachel, open up! It's your sister!
- 该死！ -开门，瑞秋，你妹妹来了。
I have to talk to you.
我要谈谈
Hi, Amy.
嗨！艾米.
- You're not Rachel. - Still sharp as a tack.
-你才不是瑞秋 -牙尖嘴利
Charlie, this is Rachel's sister Amy. Amy, this is Charlie.
查理，这是瑞秋的妹妹艾米。艾米，这是查理。
- Hi. Nice to meet you. - Hi, hi.
-很高兴认识你 -嗨！
And you are?
你是？
Ross? I grew up on your block?
罗斯，以前跟你们住一个街区
We had Thanksgiving together last year?
去年我们一起吃感恩节大餐
I had a baby with your sister?
我和你姐生了个孩子
No. I..
不，我…
Did I buy a falafel from you yesterday?
昨天我从你那儿买了中东三明治？
Yes. Yes, you did.
没错
Hi, Rachel. Here's your sister Amy.
瑞秋，你妹妹艾米来了。
She thinks I need pec implants.
她说我应该胸肌整形
Amy? Hi.
艾米？嗨！
- You remember Joey. - Yeah. Hey, sure.
-记得乔伊吗？ -当然
- The Days of our Lives guy. - That's right, yeah.
-《我们的日子》里的演员 - 对！
You are not good.
你演得真滥
Always nice to meet a fan.
见到影迷总是高兴
- So, now, what are you doing here? - Well, I have huge news.
-你来干嘛？ -我有大新闻
- Hold on. Let me check on the baby. - This is important. Can't Ella wait?
-抱歉，先看看孩子 -我有很重要的事，爱拉不能等等？
Her name is Emma.
她名叫“艾玛”
Why did you change it? Ella was so much prettier.
干嘛改名呀？爱拉好听多了！
What do I know? I just sell Middle Eastern food from a cart.
我哪晓得，我只是推着小车卖中东小吃的罢了
Hey, your English is getting better.
你英文有长进
- Oh, my God. - I know.
-天！ -对。
She may be the hottest girl I've ever hated.
她可能是我恨过的最辣的女孩
- What you working on? - Monica and Chandler's recommendation.
-你干嘛？ -莫妮卡和钱德的推荐信
I want it to sound smart, but I don't know any big words or anything.
我想让文字透着机灵劲 但深奥的词我又不会
- Why don't you use your thesaurus? - What did I just say?
-那你试试"词典" -我刚说了深奥的不会
Watch.
看着
Here, highlight the word you want to change, go under "tools"..
选中想改的词
and the thesaurus generates.. Gives.
在工具条找到"词典" 激活
Gives a whole list of choices.
“给出”候选词语表。
You can pick the word that sounds smartest.
选一个更有学问的词，就行了
My God, that's great. I'm smart.
太好了！我变机灵了！
No, no, I'm:
不，我变得
"Brainy, bright, clever." I love this thing!
“才华横溢”、“聪明伶俐” 我爱这软件
Look out, ladies! Joey Tribbiani's got the whole package!
各位，乔伊崔比阿尼 重装上阵了！
God..
天！
so beautiful.
美极了！
I know, isn't she?
是啊，她好可爱
No, I was talking about your bedding.
不，我是说你的毯子
All right, what's your news, Amy?
艾米，啥新闻？
Well..
呃…
I'm getting married.
我要结婚了
Wow! Oh, my God!
天！
- To who? - This guy.
- 和谁结婚？ - 一个男人
He has a killer apartment.
他的房子太爽了
- And..? - And it's on Fifth.
-还有呢？ -在第五大道
And the elevator opens up right into the living room.
电梯开门就到起居室
- No, what's he like? - Oh, he's okay.
-他人如何？ -他还行
Do you remember my old boyfriend Mark?
还记得我以前的男朋友马克吗？
- Yeah. - It's his dad.
-记得 -我要嫁他爹
- Wow, so he's gotta be.. - Old? Yeah.
-那他可… - 太老了?对
But he travels a lot, so he's hardly ever there.
但他常常旅行，不怎么呆在家
Sweetie, I gotta tell you, it sounds a little bit like..
你好象更喜欢他的房子
you like the apartment more than you like..
胜过...？
Myron.
马瑞.
Yeah, I told you he was old.
说过他年纪大嘛
Sit down. Sit down.
坐下
Honey, you know..
宝贝，你知道吗
I once also almost married somebody that I didn't love.
我也曾差一点嫁个我不爱的人
- Do you remember Barry? - Remember him?
-记得巴瑞吗？ -记得？
God, we used to make out all the time after you went to sleep.
你睡了以后我们常一起鬼混
Sometimes just nodding is okay.
有时点头回答就够了
But anyway, listen.
不管怎么样，听着
Not marrying Barry was the best decision that I ever, ever made.
不嫁巴瑞，是我一生最英明的决定
Honey, Amy, you deserve true love. Your soul mate is out there somewhere.
亲爱的，你应该得到真爱 你的另一半就在某处
Someone that is your age, that is smart, that is fun..
一个同龄人，聪明而有趣，你也爱他
and that you care about.
在乎他
You're right.
没错。
- You're right. I'm gonna do it. - Okay.
-没错。就这么干 - 好！
I'm gonna marry Myron and keep looking for Mr. Right.
我要嫁给马瑞，再接着找我的另一半
Okay, let's keep talking.
接着说吧
Excuse me. Anniversary.
请让让，周年纪念
Sir, could you move your nachos? They're in my seat.
先生，请把玉米片挪挪 这是我的位子
It's my anniversary.
今天是我们的周年纪念
Here we are.
一年了
- I can't believe it's been a whole year. - I know.
-真不敢相信 -是啊
This has been the best year..
这是最好的一年
- This has been the best year of my life! - Me too!
-我一辈子最快乐的一年！ -同感！
I never thought I could love someone this much!
从不知道会如此爱一个人！
I feel the same way!
同感！
You're so generous and kind, and you're amazing in bed!
你慷慨又高尚，善良，在床上又好厉害！
It's our anniversary.
我们在庆祝周年
Knicks fans, please turn your attention to the big screen on the scoreboard.
尼克斯的球迷们，请看亮分牌大屏幕这边。
Someone has a special question to ask.
有人要问一个很特别的问题
How lame. It's so tacky and impersonal.
老套！俗气！丢人现眼！
- Really? - It's the worst way to propose.
-啊？ -求婚下下策！
Excuse me.
失陪一下
I finished my recommendation. Here.
请看我写的推荐信
And I think you'll be very, very happy.
你们一定要快乐得不得了
It's the longest I ever spent on a computer without looking at porn.
从来没这么久盯着电脑，居然没去看色情站的
I don't understand.
看不懂
Some of the words a little too sophisticated for you?
有点太深奥？
It doesn't make any sense.
读不顺啊
Well, of course it does. It's smart. I used a thesaurus.
怎可能！我写得很有学问的，我用了词典啊
On every word?
每个词都用？
Yep.
没错
All right, what was this sentence originally?
这句话原本是啥意思？
"They are warm, nice people with big hearts."
他们是热心的好人
And that became, "They are humid, prepossessing Homo sapiens..
结果变成：他们是潮湿的 给人好感的智人人类
with full-sized aortic pumps."
具有标准尺寸的心脏大动脉
Yeah. Yeah. And hey, I really mean it, dude.
我真心这么想
All right, Joey, I don't think we can use this.
乔伊，恐怕我们不能用这封信
- Why not? - Well, because you signed it:
-为什么？ -因为你的签名是：
"Baby Kangaroo Tribbiani."
袋鼠宝宝：小崔 （有一个卡通袋鼠形象叫乔伊）
Why don't you stop worrying about sounding smart and just be yourself.
算了，你还是不要假装有学问 就用你的本色来写怎么样？
You don't need a thesaurus. Just write from here.
你不必用词典，要用“心”写
Your full-sized aortic pump.
让它发自你的标准尺寸的心脏大动脉？
- Amy. Hi. - I took your advice.
- 艾米！嗨！ -我听了你的话
- I left Myron. - Good for you!
-我跟马瑞分手了。 -太好了
I know. I'm Erin Brockovich.
是啊，简直像电影女主角！
Yes, you are.
对。
- I'm so proud of you. - Thank you.
-以你为荣 - 谢谢
So can I stay with you?
我能住你这里吗？
But Erin Brockovich had her own house.
电影女主角不是住她自己家吗？
Look who's back.
看谁又来啦
Why do you have bags? Why does she have bags?
你怎么带行李？ 她为什么带行李？
I'm staying with you guys.
我要和你们住一块了
- What? - We're gonna be roomies!
- 什么？ -我们是同居室友了！
Come on.
来。
- You slept out here? - Yeah.
-你睡在外面？ - 是啊！
Amy kept kicking me in her sleep, yelling, "Myron, get off!"
她梦中把我踢出来 还叫嚣什么：马瑞，滚出去！
But we're getting rid of her, right? Please tell me we're getting rid of her?
我们会把她赶走对吧？ 答应我，赶走她
- Joey, I can't do that. - Oh, come on.
-我下不了手，乔伊 -噢, 不会吧.
Last night I was finishing off a pizza, and she said:
昨晚我刚吃完一半披萨，她就说
"A moment on the lips, forever on the hips."
嘴上爽一把，屁股胖一生
I don't need that kind of talk in my house!
在我家不许说这种话！
Joey, look, I know that she's difficult..
乔伊，我知道她难相处
but I think it's really good that she's here.
但她来这里也不错
Because we'll appreciate it more when she's gone?
这样她滚蛋后我们才能更欢喜？
No, it's just.. Look, when I first moved to this city, I was a lot like her.
我刚搬来还不是一样
I was spoiled, self-centered. And you guys really took care of me.
被惯坏，自我中心 你们几个却照顾我
Yeah. Monica made us.
莫妮卡强迫我们来着
Well, whatever. I really appreciate it..
不管怎样我都很感激
because I don't think I would be the person I am today..
如果没有你们
if it wasn't for you guys.
也就没有现在的我
So I want to help Amy the way you guys helped me.
我想帮帮艾米，就像你们帮我那样
And I know it's gonna take patience, but that's okay.
我知道这需要极大的耐性，我可以
- Good morning. - Yeah.
-早 -早
That's what I'm wearing today. That's why I hung it on the door.
艾米，那是我今天要穿的衣服 所以我才挂在门上。
Oh, sweetie, you can't pull this off.
宝贝，你总不能给我扒下来
You know what? I was thinking that maybe now would be a good time..
你知道吗，现在我们也许应当坐下来
for us to sit down and, you know, talk about your future.
好好谈谈你的将来
Oh, I can't, honey. I'm gonna go get my eyebrows shaped.
我没空，我要去修眉
I am not happy.
这样的眉毛像哭丧着脸
Sure you want to eat that?
你真要吃剩下的一半？
I'm curvy and I like it!
我就是想增加曲线美，我喜欢！
- Hi. - Hi.
-嗨！ -嗨！
I just had the worst anniversary ever.
最烂的周年庆！
I doubt that. Tell her about us last year.
才不是呢 莫妮卡，给她讲讲我们去年怎么过的周年
Well, I bought Chandler a $500 watch, and he wrote me a rap song.
我给钱德买了500圆一只的表。 而他，给我写了首饶舌歌。
- Seriously? - Word.
-真的？ -是..
Mine was worse than that.
我的比你还逊
- Well, what happened? - We were at the game.
-怎么啦？ -球赛时
This guy proposed to his girlfriend on the big screen thing.
有人在大屏幕上求婚
- That is so tacky. - Well, that's what I said.
-老套！ -我也是那么说
But it turns out Mike was planning to propose to me that same way last night.
结果呢，原来麦克昨晚上就想用 这种方式向我求婚！
Oh, my God. Mike was gonna propose?
天，麦克要求婚？
- That's huge. - Do you want to marry him?
-大事件！ -你想嫁他吗？
Yeah, I really do. Yes.
当然想啦！
But after I dumped on the way he was gonna do it..
结果我那句话把他堵回去了
I don't think he'll ever ask again. I said no in Barbados, and now this?
我想他一辈子都不会求婚了。 在巴贝多我拒绝过他一次了，现在又
She's right. If I were a guy and..
没错。如果我是男人
Did I just say, "If I were a guy"?
我刚才是不是说： 如果我是男人？
You don't need him to propose to you. Maybe you could propose to him.
别等他求婚了，主动出击吧
Oh, I don't know. I don't know. Isn't that a little desperate?
哦，不知道，我又不是想嫁想疯了
I proposed to Chandler.
我向钱德求的婚
All right, moving on.
好吧，就算是
I don't think it was desperate. It was amazing.
我不觉得你想嫁想疯了，我觉得你很棒
Thank you.
谢谢。
- Well, do you think I should propose? - I think it could be kind of great.
-你们都认为我该求婚？ -那一定很棒
Absolutely. You'll love the feeling. There's nothing like it.
当然！世上再没有比求婚更美妙的感觉了！
Okay. Okay. So how should I do it?
好，就这么干
How about at a game on the big screen?
在球赛的大屏幕上告白
How about at a Foot Locker?
更老套的求婚方式如何？
What? What, he obviously thinks that's a nice way to be proposed to.
他既然选择过大屏幕求婚，可见他能接受这种方式
- Plus, he'd never suspect it. - Yeah, that does make sense.
-而且他也不会起疑心 -有理
- Okay, now, would you two like that? - Sounds good to me.
-你们会喜欢吗？ -我喜欢
But what would a guy think?
不过男性会怎么想？
- Nana's on the phone. - Wow.
-奶奶电话 - 哇！
That's interesting, since she died seven years ago.
有趣，她七年前就死了
She did?
是吗？
Who got her condo in Boca?
那她在博卡的房子归谁了？
Hello?
喂
It's our nanny.
是我们的保姆
Hi.
喂
Oh, God, I hope you feel better. Okay. Bye.
是吗，希望你早点康复。再见
That's Molly. She's sick.
是莫丽，她病了
- Can you watch Emma today? - I can't. I have back-to-back classes.
-今天你看孩子可以吗 - 不行， 我要连堂上课
Did Molly say what she had? Because my throat's been hurting.
莫丽说她生什么病？我的喉咙也不舒服
Menstrual cramps.
痛经
I don't think that's what this is.
我可能不是这毛病
- Can any of you watch Emma? - No, I'm sorry, sweetie.
-你们帮忙看着艾玛成吗？ -抱歉，亲爱的
No, I've got work, and then I'm proposing.
我要上班，还要求婚
Great. Shoot. What am I gonna do?
那怎么办
Well, I could do it.
我可以帮手
- Well, actually.. - Can I talk to you for a second?
-好 -谈谈？
I do not want her babysitting our child.
我不赞成。
- Why not? - For one thing, she keeps calling her Ella.
-为啥？ -首先，她老是把我们的孩子喊成“爱拉”
- Ella's a nice name. - Fine, we'll call the next one Ella.
-这名字也不错嘛 -好，下一胎叫"爱拉"
- The next one? - Okay.
-下一胎？ - 好
I don't want her watching our baby.
我不赞成她帮我们看孩子
Ross, I am trying to help her become a better person.
我只是想改造她
This is a huge breakthrough for her.
这是个好机会
She just offered to do something for another human being.
可以教她为别人做点事
You know, I don't know.
我不懂
Ross, I'm telling you..
罗斯，我是说
she's giving up getting her eyebrows shaped to do this, all right?
她宁愿牺牲修眉的时间看孩子
Do you understand how important that is in our world?
这件事对我们意义重大！
Listen, I couldn't help but overhear, because I was trying to.
我不小心听到你们的谈话。 因为我想听
Listen, let me do this. I really want to help you guys out.
就让我带孩子吧，我真心想帮你们
And plus, Rachel's been so wonderful to me.
而且，瑞秋对我太好了
- Absolutely. - Oh, great!
-好！ -太好了!
So how much does it pay?
付多少工钱？
How's the second draft of the letter coming?
乔伊，二稿如何？
Great. I'm finished. In fact, I just dropped it off at the agency.
杀青了，刚刚交了
- You dropped it off? - Yeah.
-交了？ - 是啊。
Can we read it? Can you print out another copy?
我们能读读吗？再打印一份给我们？
No can do, amigo.
哎呀，恐怕不行，
No, I didn't use the computer. It felt more personal to handwrite it.
没用电脑，手写的，显得更亲切
- You handwrote it? - Yeah, and don't worry.
-还手写？ -别担心
I didn't try to sound smart at all.
我根本没有装老练
See you later.
再见
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. That letter is gonna go in our file.
天，信快寄到了。
We're never gonna get a kid.
我们没指望了
We're gonna be one of those old couples..
我们会孤独终老
that collects orchids or has a lot of birds.
养花弄鸟
It's okay. You know what?
别急
I will just call the agency and tell them to throw out the letter.
我打电话给领养中心 请他们扔掉那封信
Okay, good.
好。
Hello, this is Chandler Bing.
喂，我是钱德宾
Someone just dropped off a handwritten recommendation letter and..
有人手写了一封推荐信
Okay.
对，对，好
Thank you. Goodbye.
谢谢，再见
We're screwed, aren't we?
我们完蛋了，知道吗
You know what? Just tell me on the way to the bird store.
先去买鸟，路上说给我听
- They loved it. - What?
-他们喜欢那封信 -什么？
They thought it was very smart of us to have a child write the letter.
他们说我们很聪明，叫个小孩写推荐信
They thought Joey was a child?
他们以为乔伊是小孩？
She guessed 8,9, based on his drawings.
他们看了他的画，以为他只八九岁
- Hi. - Hey, what'd you guys do today?
- 嗨！ -嗨！你们今天干嘛了？
Ella wanted to go out, so we went shopping and got some sushi.
爱拉想上街，所以我们去购物 还买了寿司
- That sounds like fun. - Yeah, not really.
-有趣 -也不是啦
Babies are dull.
BB很无趣
- Hey. Hi, how's my girl? - I'm fine.
-我家妹妹怎样了？ -我很好
And I got you a present for letting me stay with you.
我给你买了礼物，谢谢你留我住
- Ready? - Yeah.
-准备好了？ - 嗯！
You pierced her ears?
你给她穿了耳洞？
Doesn't it make her nose look smaller?
她的鼻子看来小点了吗？
You pierced her ears?
你给她穿了耳洞？
How could you do this without telling me?
竟然不征求我同意？
If I had told you, then it wouldn't have been a surprise, now would it?
我若先告诉你，就不是惊喜了
I think she looks cute.
我想她看来很可爱
But I am wrong.
但我错了
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Here comes Ross. He's gonna flip out.
天，罗斯会发飚的
Why, did something happen to his falafel cart?
中东女孩不能穿耳洞吗？
- Hey, guys. - Ross!
- 嗨，各位！. - 罗斯！
Hi, Emma. Why is she wearing her hat so low?
嗨，艾玛。 她的帽子干嘛压这么低？
- She can barely see. - I don't really want her to see.
-她都看不见了 -人家不想她看见嘛
Why not?
为啥？
Because there are so many terrible sights in this world.
世界太可怕
Like war. Or that thing in Joey's refrigerator. Remember?
有战争，还有乔伊冰箱里那玩意儿
It was in a milk carton, but it looked like meat?
一只牛奶盒，但看来像块肉
Come here. Come here.
快来，快来
There she is. Hi.
看她多乖
- What? - Nothing.
-怎么啦？ -没啥
Hi.
嗨！
What..?
什么?
- Please tell me those are clip-ons! - Oh, they're real.
-那是夹上去的？ -是戴上的
Did she do this to her?
是她干的？
I told you we shouldn't have left Emma with her!
我早说过不能把艾玛交到她手上！
I know, I know. And you were right, Ross.
我知道了！你说得对
Okay? You are so irresponsible! I am never letting you babysit again!
你太不负责！ 绝不再让你看孩子！
You know what? This kid needs me, okay?
你们知道吗？ 她需要我！
- She needs to have a cool, fun aunt. - I'm a cool, fun aunt.
-她需要一个又酷又有趣的阿姨！ -我就是！
Okay.
好吧
Hey! Monica can be cool and fun at organized indoor projects.
莫妮卡就是又酷又有趣，而且有条有理！
All I wanted to do was help you try to figure out what to do with your life.
我只不过想帮你想清楚你将来想干什么！
This is how you repay me?
结果呢，你还是小孩子？
I don't need you to help me. I already know what I'm gonna do with my life.
谁稀罕你帮忙。我自己想好了
- Oh, yeah? Since when? - Since today.
-是吗？几时想好的？ -今天
I am going to be a baby stylist.
我要当BB时尚专家！
- What? - That's not a thing!
-啊？ -有这职业吗？
Well, it should be.
应该有！
I'm gonna help babies learn how to accessorize..
我要教BB如何穿戴
what colors to wear, what clothes are slimming.
选衣裳的颜色，什么衣服较瘦身
- Babies don't care if they're slim! - Enter Amy.
- BB才不想苗条呢！ -如何像艾米一样美！
- Amy, I.. I just.. I just wanna.. - What? What are you gonna do?
- 艾米, 我要… -你想怎样？
No more falafel for you!
罚你永世没有三明治吃！
Great game, huh?
比赛很精彩
- Why do you keep looking at the screen? - I'm not. I'm praying.
-你怎么老瞄大屏幕？ -没，我在祷告
Please let the Knicks win.
请让尼克斯队赢吧
Thank you, Thor.
谢谢！托尔(北欧神话中的雷神)
- Where are you going? - I'm going to the bathroom.
-你上哪儿？ -嘘嘘去
- Well, I think you should wait. - Why?
-等一会 -为啥？
Well, if you don't hold it in, you don't get all the nutrients.
如果不憋一会，你就无法摄取所有养分
Knicks fans, please turn your attention to the big screen on the scoreboard.
尼克斯球迷，请注意积分牌大屏幕
Someone has a special question to ask.
有人要问特别的问题
Mike Hannigan, will you marry me?
麦克汉那根，娶我好吗？
Get a load of this. She's proposing to him!
看啊，她向他求婚！
Guess we know who wears the pants in that family.
到底谁更有种？
Well, that's not very enlightened.
不要误导观众！
Boo us? Boo you!
不许嘘我们！
Odin will smite you!
你们去死！
Hello? Yeah, this is Joey Tribbiani.
喂？我就是乔伊崔比阿尼
Oh, hi.
哦，嗨！
Well, I'm glad you liked my letter.
真高兴你喜欢我的信
No, my mommy and daddy aren't home right now.
我爸妈不在家
Okay, bye-bye.
再见
She was nice.
她真慈祥
Joey, get Amy's bags. She is moving out.
乔伊，把艾米的箱子拿出来，她要搬走了
- You're kicking me out? - You put holes in my baby's ears.
-你把妹妹踢出家门？ -你给我的BB穿耳洞！
At least now people will know she's a girl!
不然大家怎么知道她是女孩？
I can't believe I ever even tried to help you.
不敢相信，我竟然想过要帮你！
- You are so beyond help! - You know what?
-你不可救药！ - 你知道吗？
Ever since I got here, you have been nothing but negative.
这次见面你在否定我的一切！
- Excuse me? - You didn't want me..
-啊？ -你不准我…
to marry the old guy with the great apartment.
不准我嫁有豪宅的老头
Then I tried to help your daughter de-emphasize her flaws..
我想帮你把你女儿的鼻子变小点
and suddenly I'm the bad guy?
结果吃力不讨好？
- Joey, where are those bags? - She has a lot of crap!
-乔伊，行李怎么还没搬出来？ -她的破玩意太多了
You know? When I moved in here, I thought, "This will be so great.
我刚搬来时，还想着太好了
Just us sisters back together again like when we were kids."
憧憬着姐妹团聚 像童年那样
Except without that stupid Jill.
而且没有该死的吉尔捣乱
Who has gotten fat, by the way.
她变肥了
Seriously?
真的？
Mom said she gained, like,15 pounds.
妈说吉尔肥了15磅
- Hips or thighs? - Ass and face.
-屁股和大腿长肉了？ -屁股和脸
Oh, my God! I thought she was on Atkins.
天啊，她不是节食吗？
She was. Carbs found her.
本来是，后来被男人甩了
See? This is what I wanted.
看，这才像姐妹
Two sisters talking about real stuff.
真心交谈
Oh, I can give you that.
哦，我可以这样
- You can? - Yeah.
- 你可以？ - 是的。
I kept trying to make you a better person, but you're..
我老想改造你。实际上
You're already a pretty perfect version of what you are.
你本来就接近完美了
Thank you.
谢谢你
You gotta admit, Emma does look cute.
必须承认，艾玛真可爱
- Did you just say, "Emma"? - Oh, I'm sorry. Ella.
-你刚说“艾玛”？ -对不起， 爱拉
Sis, you wanna go bring Jill some pasta?
姐, 你要给吉尔带意大利面?
Come on, Amy. Now, that's just wrong.
艾米. 那些是错的.
Her true weakness was garlic bread.
她真的怕的是大蒜奶油面包片.
That woman didn't know what she was talking about, Mike.
赛场里那家伙真是乱讲
Obviously, you have balls.
你当然有种
- Please, let's forget the whole thing. - I would love it.
-忘了算了 -你能忘最好
- Consider it forgotten. - Thank you.
- 已经忘了 - 谢谢
But just so you know..
不过你知道...
However and whenever you decide to propose, I promise I'll say yes.
不管你何时、以何方式求婚 我保证答应
Whether, you know, it's at a basketball game..
不管是篮球赛
or in skywriting..
还是写在空中
or, you know, like some lame guy in a cheesy movie..
或是像有部滥电影里
who hides it in the cake.
把求婚信藏在蛋糕里
It's in the cake, isn't it?
是蛋糕对吧？
Where else would lame Mr. No Balls hide it?
没种的男人还会有什么好点子吗
What's the matter with me? Why do I keep ruining this?
我是怎么了？怎么老提这个！
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry. - No, it's my fault.
-对不起嘛 -是我错
I keep trying to propose in these stupid ways..
我老用愚蠢的方式求婚
and I just wanna tell you I love you, and I wanna spend my life with you..
我只是想告诉你 我爱你，我想和你度过余生
- I'm gonna do this now. - Oh, my God.
-我现在求婚 -天啊
- Phoebe, I.. - Wait. Oh, wait.
-菲比 -暂停
Oh, no.
暂停
Okay.
好了。
Ready? Okay.
可以了？
Phoebe, I love you.
菲比，我爱你。
There's no one else in the world I would ask to marry me three times.
这个世界只有你我会三次求婚
But I want to take care of you..
我想照顾你
have babies with you..
和你生儿育女
and grow old with you.
一起变老
Phoebe Buffay, will you marry me?
菲比布费，你愿意嫁我吗
Yes.
我愿意！
- I love you. - I love you more.
-我爱你 -我爱你更多
Not possible.
不可能
She's gonna be Mrs. No Balls!
她是“没种夫人”了
So how's the baby-styling business going?
“BB时尚专家”好当吗？
Not that great.
行情不大好
It's almost as if people don't want to hear that their babies are ugly.
好象大家都不爱听见他们的BB丑
That's shocking.
吃惊
There's Ross. Hey, Ross.
那不是罗斯吗？罗斯！！！
Hello, Ross?
你好，罗斯！
He's rude.
真没教养